<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>muse on Notes</title>
    <link>/categories/muse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in muse on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 20:37:33 +0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/categories/muse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>/posts/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 20:37:33 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Your uncanny faith in what we have, what developed along the way, to uncertainties ahead. Is most of my muse these days. I did not bring anything to the table, nothing beyond necessities. Yet you morphed whatever scrap we had, mold its concoction of an existence to a meaningful whole. You could have moved on, you could have ended it all, you can still just fade to a life of your own.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppeteer</title>
      <link>/posts/puppeteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 22:05:47 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/puppeteer/</guid>
      <description>Puppets! He mutters, not free, in a monolog, while unpacking the stage. Our biase, our presupposition, our belief, he continued. Its a story, add a pinch of salt at will. You can not see my harness, am I at my own will? with a concerned look on his face, while he sets two of his characters on the stage. These were not elaborate, those puppets, yet distinguishable, a male and a female.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to Muse</title>
      <link>/posts/dear-muse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 12:40:30 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dear-muse/</guid>
      <description>Dear Muse,
Stuck in an endless loop of writing this letter and deleting it. Every time with a slightly different meaning, the goal? I am not clear on that. I simply can not get a grip on this untangled mess. Few of those letters had our differences listed, few emotionally charged, few aggressive, some more apologetic than others. That is not all, they even had profound shit like the utilitarian conclusion and stoic viewpoints.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaos</title>
      <link>/posts/chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 11:47:01 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/chaos/</guid>
      <description>In the midst of chaos I reside, a distant observer to my own life.
I am on a thought created dungeon, this calm endless sea.
Rowing voices of my oarsmen into the abyss,
me expressionless, at the bow of this ship.
Staring at the shimmering reflection of this star lit sky.
Every time I close my eyes, deserts, mountains,
lush green planes, life at its apex, all that is unseen.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
